contentior.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Policy

“Contentior” is a quality service initiative. We respect your privacy and this privacy policy is designed to assist you in understanding our philosophy. This Privacy Policy applies to information submitted via the web forms, either for clients or suppliers as well as personal information communicated via email with the markerting department.From time to time we may add new features, or services to the Contentior Network. Please note that this Policy will apply to all services under this brand name.This Privacy Policy incorporates by reference Contentior’s ‘Payment Policies‘, ‘Terms of Use‘, its ‘Supplier’s Guidelines‘, and any ‘Contentior‘ licensing agreement to which You are a party.

BY ACCESSING, BROWSING & USING CONTENTIOR NETWORK OR OTHERWISE SUBMITTING INFORMATION TO THIS SERVICE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND AND AGREED TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND ANY OTHER TERMS OF USE PUBLICLY PRESENTED BY CONTENTIOR. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, PLEASE DO NOT SUBMIT YOUR INFORMATION CONTENTIOR.

Your Privacy Rights.

Under the laws of some jurisdictions, you may be entitled to request disclosure regarding how Contentior uses personal information for direct marketing purposes (”Information-Sharing Disclosure”). To the extent required by applicable law, Contentior shall provide the Information-Sharing Disclosure to its end users upon rightful request made in writing or by electronic mail to the following address: marketing@contentior.com

All information collected, is in order to serve your online content needs better and provide you with attentive and consistent customer service, Contentior may collect several types of information, including both personal and non-personal information as described below. The information Associated Content collects depends on how you choose to use this network.

### 1\. “Non- Personally Identifiable Information” Collected.

  * The Contentior Network will not track or collect any information about your general web surfing habits.
  * “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a web site transfers to a visitor’s hard drive. Your Web browser may have an option that allows you to accept & reject cookies, or receive notification when a cookie is sent. You should note that the use of restrictive browser settings may limit the functionality available to your browser while using our service. Any cookies and other Internet traffic tracking technologies utilized in connection with the Contentior are not designed to gather any Personally Identifiable Information.

### 2\. “Personally Identifiable Information” Collected.

  * Personally Identifiable Information about you is not collected unless you provide it yourself to Contentior.

For example, when you submit your email address for communication purposes or offer your contact information with the intention of being a content provider, you will be requested to provide certain Personally Identifiable Information. The information we collect about you through such sources may vary, depending upon the nature of the services you chosse, to fulfill your request we must need some basic information like: First and Last name, Email address, Contact Number, Instant Messanger Id and/or other identifying information that permits Contentior tointeract with you.

  * In general, Contentior collects Personally Identifiable Information from users of Contentior in connection with access to certain online areas services, during 
    1. registration for certain online services and tools such as content submission, payment information,
    2. registration for special communications, such as email updates, “Forget Password” and special communication mails;
    3. user surveys(occassional)
    4. events,
    5. promotions.

Your Personally Identifiable Information is stored on Contentior secure servers.

We may gather data about the areas of our Network that you visit or access.

However we will not use any of this navigational data about how you “as an individual user” use our Network or share any of this data with any other third parties. However, we do use this navigational data in an aggregate, non-personal form to understand how our users as a group uses our site.

### 3\. Use of Information Collected.

(a) Contentior uses Personally Identifiable Information to customize and personalize content displayed on the your pages, and to send you – emails, notification mails, and other materials, or for the purposes for which it is submitted by you; i.e – to complete transactions or to fulfill services you have requested, as well as for the cases when we need to contact you when processing your requested transaction.

Further, your Personally Identifiable Information, including any query or feedback will be retained in our database, for the purpose of evaluating and improving our customer-relation and assistance programs.

(b) Contentior also may use this information to identify and develop products and services that may be of interest to you within or outside this product line.

(c) We do not sell individual customer names or other Personally Identifiable Information to third parties and have no intention of doing so in the future.

(d) Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, Contentior does not disclose or release your Personally Identifiable Information to any third party:

i. for compliance purposes, such as immigration and customs control, security, and legal support;

ii. in connection with legal requests from government authorities for any legal process;

iii. to perform payment verifications, debt reporting or collection, or to otherwise protect the rights or property of Taragna(Parent body of Contentior) its employees, customers, or end users.

(e) You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information (e.g., user name, email address) on any media or web-page which is not associated or originated from Contentior Network, such information may be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. We have no control over this use of your Personally Identifiable Information. We advise users to be especially careful in such public areas about disclosing

Personally Identifiable Information, such as full name, home address, or contact number.

### 4.Below are more details about the Personally Identifiable Information we may gather from you and how we may use it.

**(a) Email Newsletters.**

We offer email newsletters to its users who registers as supplier. We will use your email address to send you only the specific newsletter(s) that you signed up for. If you want to update your email address or stop receiving centain kind of newsletters,

please send us a mail to marketing@contentior.com

and we will act according to your specification. We may contact you regarding account status, changes to this Policy, our content agreements or other terms of use, to confirm your registration or for any other business reason related to your use of this service.

**(b) Co-registration with other Networks.**

As a Member, we may offer you the ability to co-register with selected third-party partner sites. In some instances where Contentior provides co-registration in future, the co-registration partners allow you to opt-out of their membership. If you choose to co-register with our partners and accept their terms of service, then yo are automatically registered as a Member of their web sites and your Personally Identifiable Information is transferred to those organizations. As a result, you may

receive information from one of these web sites as any of their Members would. We advise you to review the privacy and data collection policies of the third-party partner sites for further information. In order to cancel your membership with any of these partners you will need to go directly to the partner’s site.

**(c) Advertisers.**

We may send you emails on behalf of our advertisers. If you opt to receive information from our advertisers they may send you advertisements or other notices, via email.

**(d) Promotions.**

We may ask you for Personally Identifiable Information at other times, including, but not limited to, when you enter contests or promotions sponsored by Associated Content. If you choose to enter sweepstakes, contests or promotions sponsored by a third party, the Personally Identifiable Information you provide will be subject to the

privacy policy of the third-party sponsor. We encourage you to check the applicable third-party policy before providing any Personally Identifiable Information.

**(e) Surveys and User Research.**

Contentior may conduct email and web-delivered surveys from time to time, as well as instant polls, to gather information about our users, & their satisfaction level with our services. Participation in these surveys and polls is entirely optional. You have no obligation to respond to them. We share only the aggregate results of these surveys, not Personally Identifiable Information to better understand your wants

& needs and act accordingly. We may also use some of the Personally Identifiable Information that you provide in these surveys to help us understand your interests and to make the Associated ourlself more useful to you.

**(f)Availing of Services.**

When you make a purchase decision for any of our offered services from Contentior, we may require Personally Identifiable Information such as Full name, email id, telephone number, Instant message Id, PayPal Id and some other personal information which are needed for uninterrupted delivery of services. We, at Contentior will not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, including billing information, except to the extent necessary to complete your transaction.

**(g) Payment Information (for Suppliers only)**

As a supplier, you will be required to submit certain Personally Identifiable Information as it relates to payment. Contentior shall not disclose, sell, lease, rent or otherwise share your any of your information, including account or transaction information, except to the extent necessary to ensure that there is no fraud related to your account or to verify your identity.

**(j) Legal Authorities.**

As and where needed, we may disclose Personally Identifiable Information to Legal authorities, in cases when we strongly believe for valid reasons, that it is necessary to identify someone who may be violating our policies, User Agreements or other terms of use, or who may be a threat to Contentior, or for personal safety. Contentior may disclose Personally Identifiable Information to comply with valid legal process such as a duly issued search warrant, or court order.

### 5\. Updation/modificaion of Personally Identifiable Information.

As a service renderer you can request to review and edit any personal information that has been provided by you, to Contentior at any time by making such request in writing to: marketing@contentior.com

### 6\. Security of Personal Information:

(a) We, at Contentior take all commercially possible precautions for safety

of information and has implemented latest reasonable technical measures to protect your valuable personal information, against the risks of unauthorized access, unwanted disclosure, and unlawful interception of Personally Identifiable

Information submitted to us.

(b) Once you fill up the registration form in our site, & your information is received from our end, we use maximum possible efforts to limit access to Personally

Identifiable Information about you to only few of those, who really need access to it, to provide the requested services & to offer opportunities that may be of matching with your interest. Please be aware that your email transmissions or any other communications to Contentior, that contains Personal Information may be unlawfully intercepted or accessed by third parties while being sent to us. So, we

at Contentior does not guarantee that your Personally Identifiable Information is completely secure and safe from such all possible risks. We advice to use latest

antispyware & security system in your computer to save yourself from being a victim of web-forgery.

### 7\. Consent to Privacy Policy.

By accessing or using the our services or otherwise providing information as described above to Contentior, you are giving your consent that you have read & understood all terms & conditions, as stated in this Privacy Policy. Contentior reserves the right, at any time, with or without notice, to add, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by publicly posting such change, by updating or

modifying this page. Any such change, updation or modification will be applicable immediately upon public posting on the Contentior site. By continuing to access, browse, or use the service or otherwise by providing information as described by us, you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, as amended to date.

### 8\. Further Questions.

If you have any question or concern regarding this Privacy Policy or about any of the information submitted to Contentior, please go to “contact us” page and send us your query.
